<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DoSell]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DoSell]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/dosell/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 19:28:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/dosell/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>DOSELL SERVICES   WE CONNECT THE PUZZLE PIECES TO YOUR SUCCESS   DO WHAT YOU LOVE – WE DO THE REST Frustrated that the puzzle pieces of your business aren’t connecting? Our hub of specialists fix internal operations, reduce business stress and costs, and enable you to expand to new markets and grow your business to a global scale.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dosell/dosell-services-we-connect-the-puzzle-pieces-to-your-succe/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">af0d76c6-c193-474d-9141-9755d062de1b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 19:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>BUSINESS ARCHITECTURE Every structure needs a solid foundation from which to build and expand. After a thorough consultation we help streamline your organization by aligning strategic goals and objectives that will improve your business processes and capabilities, power up your business model and boost your company efficiency.   Our specialties include: Customer insight Business process evaluation and redesign Ideation Technology scouting Product development strategy Business model generation Value proposition design DOSELL DESIGN HUB Great design makes all the difference. It brings ideas to life, makes products stand out and differentiates a brand. Most importantly, the right design facilitates the transition of a unique idea in to a functional product when balanced with the right engineering and manufacturing resources. Design covers a wide spectrum of disciplines – and we have them covered!   Our specialties include: Identity design Product design Industrial design Product Development   VIRTUAL PROTOTYPING LAB Virtual product prototyping helps verify concepts at an early stage. It reduces the time of product design iteration and identifies potential mistakes before advancing to the next phase, saving time and resources.   Our specialties include: CAD model pre-verification based on engineering models CAD pre-verification based on international standards (in beta) Complete prototyping based on your brief and documentation ONE-STOP SHOP ENGINEERING HUB Our cost-effective solution to new product development includes verifying CAD, reducing parts and optimizing designs for manufacture.   Our specialties include: Finite Element Analysis (FEA) CAE Services Industrial Optimization Service (IOS) Design of Experience (DOE) Engineering consulting Process simulation Design of special purpose machinery, robot cells, pick and place automats Assembly line, and robotics for production industry Rapid Prototyping   OPERATIONAL EXCELLENCE LAB The discipline of Virtual Ergonomics Verification was created to improve productivity, efficiency and quality, and to reduce occupational disease, sick-leave and the fluctuation of employees. With automatic inertial motion-capture sensors, the movement of assembly lines and workplaces are analyzed to make processes easier to evaluate.   Our specialties include: Manufacturing optimization Workplace monitoring; conceptive and corrective analysis Digital Ergonomy SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT HUB Great code and enterprise architecture can boost your company’s efficiency, because software is the foundation of any business.   Our specialties include: Back-end architecture development Enterprise Architecture Development end-to-end based on Java technology Large scale CMS, E-commerce system development OSGI-based RAD technology (framework) Rapid application development In-depth cryptography and software security solutions Java Scrum team outsourcing   SOFTWARE & IT SECURITY EVALUATION LAB We analyze your software, check your code secure and then evaluate it to prove its value.   Our specialties include: Common Criteria Software Audit IT Audit ISO27001 Smart Card evaluation GLOBAL MARKET ADVISORY CONSULTANCY Our Global Market Advisory Consultancy seamlessly links local know-how and networks with your company’s market growth plan. Carefully selected leading players from key advisory segments - including accounting, tax, investment banking, law and corporate finance - will open doors to new businesses. With this service you can easily navigate different local regulations, testing marks and laws, country by country.   Our specialties include: A global network of 20 offices across 18 countries and five continents, and growing. More than 500 business minded, market leading advisors, lawyers. An integrated, seamless service with one point of contact, supported by a unified international team. Careful alignment of complimentary practices, such as tax, accounting and consultancy, creating a one-stop-shop, tailor-made solution for your needs. The benefits of a boutique service combined with the advantages of a full-scale service provider. We are specialists in helping companies expand into China.   We can help you connect with new clients, build a global brand, grow into international markets, and find investment opportunities, access to financing or find investors. We will be your business partners.  . © 2015 DoSell Member firms of DoSell are independent design, engineering firms</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dosell/business-architecture-every-structure-needs-a-solid-foundati/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">534f7f06-4228-458f-9269-f01d5b675b78</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 19:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>SERVICE ENGINEERING IS IN OUR DNA Helping Companies Grow through Carefully Audited Comprehensive Services OUR MISSION & VISION      DoSell was founded by a diverse group of professionals, who despite specializing in different fields and having varied business backgrounds, had all experienced similar frustrations while trying to achieve the business and operational excellence that leads to success.   Yes, we’ve been there! From our own experiences in the enterprise sector, we know all too well the challenges that today’s business leader faces, from quality issues, design conflicts, schedule delays to the lack of proper management - never mind their sales and marketing departments constantly working under pressure to fill the top of the sales funnel. These burdens combined make it hard to focus on keeping clients happy and establish a good reputation. And a happy customer and great reputation will always be your best sales tool.   At DoSell, we are driven by a simple mantra: ‘Solve the business leaders’ daily problems’. Because we understand that while you may excel in one element of business, without the others, success will remain elusive.   Our goal is to help overwhelmed company owners and leaders reduce their business stress and costs with our open source hub of experts, in order to acclerate growth and achieve greater efficiency, and to prepare them to build their business to a global scale.   Our mission is to provide a seamless solution for companies that are finding it challenging to fit the puzzle pieces of success together, despite having world-class products ready to market that can change lives.   We believe in radical project execution and a pleasant customer journey. And we strive to deliver results customized to our client’s individual.   We founded DoSell because we knew we could make a difference. And we look forward to proving it to you!   Tibor Zahorecz – Founder, Managing Partner  OUR PEOPLE & CULTURE         DoSell is all about teamwork. The collaboration between our in house team and our carefully selected hub of global service providers who are proven in their field of expertise makes for powerful solution. Each and every one of us share a common goal: the commitment to providing our clients with expert partners to help them achieve their goals. We consult, we identify and we fix. Together.   FOUNDERS  Tibor Zahorecz Founder DoSell & Managing Partner  ‘I became passionate about easing the stress of fellow company leaders’ lives after experiencing the frustration of not receiving proper services from providers for my business.’   Adel Erdosi Co-Founder DoSell - (Managing Partner Everit)  ‘We founded DoSell with a shared vision and commitment to help business leaders grow their business by bringing the best solution under the roof.’   Dr. Rupert Varnai Co-Founder DoSell - (CEO Cathay Associates)  ‘When you work with us, we are more than just a simple service provider. We work closely with you to determine your real organization problems and requirements.’   Gabor Kiglics DoSell Partner  (Founder/M.D. Econ Engineering)  Peter L. Molnar DoSell Partner  (Co-Founder & MD Maform)  Bela Batitzi DoSell Partner (Managing Partner Vive Human)   TEAM  Eniko Gall DoSell Back Office Manager  Peter Tölgyesi Head of Scrum PMO Everit  Balazs Zsoldos Head of Software Development and R&D Everit  Judit Huszar Communication Expert and Designer  Akos Horvath CFD Manager Econ Engineering  Marton Graf FEM Manager Econ Engineering  Tibor Meszes Engineering Manager at Econ  Laszlo Ordogh Co-founder & CTO Vivetech  Csaba Szeredy Co-Founder & CEO Vivetech  Gabor Hornyak Head of Software Evaluation Lab & Common Criteria Expert  Geza Csire Co-Founder & Head of Production Design Maform © 2015 DoSell Member firms of DoSell are independent design, engineering firms</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dosell/service-engineering-is-in-our-dna-helping-companies-grow-thr/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8dca46c7-2bef-4433-a92b-bef21b49c1a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 19:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>DoSell Flow – Making Experience   Bring your Ideas to Life & Scale Globally DoSell as one-stop-shop end-to-end system factory: in addition to audited service providers and our internal service innovation engine, take care of your business architect, design, engineering and global market access advisory needs. Let us be more than your outsourcing partners: we help you connect with new clients, build a global brand, grow into international markets, find shorter design cycle, access to excellent software development companies.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dosell/dosell-flow-making-experience-bring-your-ideas-to-life-and/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b0dcc-f0f8-49dd-8e53-77270147a309</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 19:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>